(盐颈 谢谢光临)
人生切割术
第二季 第八集
(德文斯科特来电)
你听说北松那件破事了吗
You hear about that clusterfuck up on North Pine?
达驰史蒂文斯的孩子
Dutch Stevens' kid.
到底是怎么把2吨重的铲雪机弄翻的
How the fuck do you flip a two-ton snow plow?
因为愚蠢
With stupidity.
有其父必有其子
The apple don't fall far from the gutter.
你人真好
Well, that's kind of you.
当我们请的
On the house.
谢谢
Thank you.
嗨 萝丝
Hey, Rose.
要续杯吗
You want a refill?
欢迎你随时给我添
You can top me off anytime.
我喜欢你的新发型
I like the new do.
非常时髦
Très chic.
哈蒙妮科贝尔
Harmony Cobel.
我的老天
Well, flip my toboggan.
要喝杯咖啡吗
You want coffee?
不了
No.
就餐的顾客才能坐下
Tables are for paying customers.
好吧 那就请我喝杯咖啡
Fine. Then buy me a coffee.
这座镇子比我记忆中更老旧了
The town is older than I remember.
更破败
Frailer.
是 因为几年前的市场调整
Yeah, well, with the market readjustment from a few years ago
利率波动
and the fluctuating interest rates,
一些核心的基建投资被缩减了
there was a retrenchment from some of the core infrastructure investments.
我需要你帮个忙
I need a favor.
但不能在这里说
But not here.
我们去工厂见
Meet me at the factory.
- 嘿 朵特 帮我关店 - 好
- Hey, Dot. Close up for me. - Sure.
(滴壶咖啡馆)
(卢蒙工业)
你知道你让我来这里有多扯吗
You know how fucked it is to ask me to come here?
我需要你载我去找茜茜
I need you to drive me to Sissy's.
不行 抱歉
No, thanks.
如果他们在监视房子 一定会认出我的车
If they're watching the house, they'll recognize my car.
你惹了多少麻烦
How much trouble are you in?
不少
Enough.
你知道她仍笃信九项原则吗
You know she still lives by the nine?
我猜也是
I assumed.
那你就知道她是这里的边缘人
Then you know she's a fucking pariah here.
你可以留在卡车上
You can stay in the truck.
我必须拿一件东西
I need to get something.
我凭什么要帮你
Why would I help you with anything?
我们曾经是密友
We were once chums.
旧日的同事应该互相支持
Old colleagues lift each other up.
同事
Colleagues?
那叫该死的童工
Child fucking labor.
基尔和伊莫金在乙醚厂相识
Kier and Imogene met at the Ether Mill,
你知道的吧
you know that?
她当时咳嗽得厉害吗
Was she hacking up a lung at the time?
我能从你呼出的气息里闻出来
I can smell it on your breath.
真可悲
Pathetic.
去你的
Fuck you.
帮不帮随你
You can help me or not.
但我不会当你仇恨的出气筒
But I'll not be the punching dummy for your resentments.
(德文斯科特来电)
安全了
Coast is clear.
你嗑药嗑得已经云里雾里了
You're higher than a bearded vulture.
帮我问候她全家啊
Tell her to drop dead for me.
这里不欢迎你
You are not welcome here.
你这是私闯民宅
This is trespass.
我会报警
I have a mind to call the authorities.
我不要那个吸白粉的进入我的地盘
I do not want that huff peddler on my property.
他上瘾都是因为你
You gave him his thirst for it.
你撒谎成性
You've a liar's mouth.
(哈蒙妮 12岁 11岁 10岁)
你要不要下来 告诉我这一切是怎么回事
Do you want to come down here and tell me what this is all about?
(卢蒙乙醚 季度上进员工)
(第四季度 愿景之年)
(青年见习教务长 “茜茜” 茜莉思汀科贝尔)
你把我的东西放哪儿了
What have you done with my things?
卖了 卖给穷人了
Sold. To the poor.
那不是你的东西 你没权卖
They weren't yours to sell.
住在这房子里的是我
I sit in this house.
不是你
You do not.
有谁来过这里吗
Has anyone been here?
没人来这里
No one comes here.
那有谁打过电话
Or telephoned?
有个叫达蒙德先生的
A Mr. Drummond.
他想要什么
And what did he want?
小老鼠 你做了什么
What have you done, little mouse?
哈蒙妮
Harmony!
我想要母亲房间的钥匙
I want the key to Mother's room.
那个房间会一直锁着 直到记得她的人都站在基尔一边
That room stays shut until all who remember her sit with Kier.
你明白的
You know this.
把钥匙给我
Give me the key.
为什么你只会给我的生命带来悲哀
Why do you bring nothing but woe into my life?
不 给这个家带来悲哀诅咒的人是你
No, it is you who cursed this house with woe.
我不跟你吵
I will not have this quarrel.
她临终前说了什么
What were her last words?
孩子 别逼我
Child, do not test me.
她说了什么
What were they?
你拔掉管子后 她什么都没说
She said nothing after you pulled the tube from her gullet.
她从痛苦中解脱 眼中有感激
There was gratitude in her eyes to be freed from her suffering.
如果她生前是信徒就好了
If only she had been a believer.
也许她就会在九项原则中找到慰藉
Perhaps she would have found solace in the nine.
你不用像我一样日复一日听着她的喘息
You didn't have to listen to her wheezing as I did, day after day.
如果我不是在学校 我会亲自照顾她的
I would have cared for her myself, had I not been at school.
学校是你的归属
Where you belonged.
我甚至连告别的机会都没有
I didn't even get to say goodbye.
你的学业更加重要
Your studies were more important.
伊根先生看到你具备基尔的品质
Mr. Eagan saw Kier in you.
真的
He really did.
冬潮奖学金...
And the Wintertide Fellowship--
就算是在工厂时 你也是最勤恳努力的见习生
Even at the factory, no apprentice was more industrious than you.
结果你却令人大失所望
Such a disappointment you've proven to be.
达蒙德和你说了什么
What did Drummond tell you?
回去乞求原谅吧 孩子
Return and plead forgiveness, child.
伊根将原谅你
The Eagans will grant it.
同时也赐我仁慈
And show me mercy,
像你对母亲所做的那样
just like you did with Mother.
钥匙在哪
Where is the key?
你在里面只会找到痛苦
All you will find in there is pain.
到底在哪儿
Where is it?
我找到了
I found it!
开啊
Come on.
别 别靠近
Don't! Stand away!
把你的脏手拿开
Get your harpy hands off me.
这里不欢迎你 低贱的毒品奴
You've no salutation here, you blighted snuff slave.
好吧 我也很想你 你身上一股腐朽味
All right, I missed you too. You smell like crow skin.
我会打电话叫人 我发誓
I'll phone somebody. I swear it!
是 把大家都叫来 我们可以开场派对
Yeah, call everyone. We'll have a fucking kegger.
这是一个纯净的房子
This is a pure house.
后退 否则我把你扔到海里
Back off or I'll put you in the bay!
怎么了 发生了什么
What is it? What happened?
没什么 我来找你
Nothing. Came to get you.
她不太开心
She's not too happy about it.
你看到什么了吗
Did you see something?
没有 但卡车上冷死了 我得回去了
No, but it's cold as shit in the truck, and I gotta get back.
我必须找到
I have to find it.
找到什么
Find what?
给我一点时间思考一下
Just give me a minute just to think.
我喜欢她
I liked her.
你根本不了解她
You barely knew her.
她比我更恨卢蒙
She hated Lumon more than I did.
我只需了解这一点就够了
That's all I needed to know.
至少她不用再和茜茜一起生活了
At least she doesn't have to live with Sissy anymore.
想一起嗑药吗
You wanna get high?
哇
Wow.
我八岁后就没干过这事了
I haven't done that since I was eight.
你准备好看守大罐十小时吗
You ready to man the vat for ten hours?
你卖了它 太可惜了
It's so shameful that you sell it.
我觉得不在这里
I don't think it's here.
你找的东西
What you're looking for.
滚出去
Get out of here!
她不会扔掉的
She wouldn't throw it away.
(麦特伊根女子学校 年度回忆)
(加油 孩子们)
(荣誉和奖项)
(毕业生代表 哈蒙妮科贝尔)
(杰姆伊根 冬潮奖学金)
(哈蒙妮科贝尔 冬潮奖学金获得者)
(杰姆伊根冬潮奖学金)
(哈蒙妮科贝尔 诡术之年)
找到了吗
Find it?
准备出发 小心我的头
Get the truck ready. And watch my head.
我走了 别告诉他们我来过
I'm going. Don't tell them I was here.
我绝不会对伊根家族的管家说假话
I would never bear falsity to a steward of the Eagans.
卢蒙毁了这个镇
Lumon destroyed this town.
你不需要向他们效忠
You owe them no loyalty.
工厂建立之前 这个小镇根本不存在
There was no town before the factory.
你自己的职务呢
And what about your own employ?
你所拥有的一切 都是伊根家族的恩赐 你必须以效忠回报
Everything that you have, you owe back to the Eagans as fealty.
效忠
Fealty?
是我的
Mine!
我的设计
My designs!
电路图
Circuit blueprint...
基础代码
Base code...
紧急加班
Overtime contingency...
格拉斯哥屏障 所有一切
Glasgow block. All of it.
杰姆伊根是发明者
Jame Eagan was the inventor.
我也听说了
So I've heard.
了不起
Extraordinary.
你为什么从没提过
Why have you never spoken of this?
人们都说基尔的知识属于所有人
It was told Kier's knowledge is for all.
那是真的
That is true.
如果我要求将功劳归于自己 就会被放逐
That if I sought credit, I would be banished.
我希望你像她一样死得那么痛苦
I hope you die as painfully as she did.
拔去管子的是她 不是我
It was her hand that removed the tube, not mine.
不
No!
你母亲是个胆小鬼
Your mother was a coward.
她的病在灵魂 更甚于躯体
More sick in the soul than in the body.
充满恶意和仇恨
Filled with malice and resentment.
我不信你
I don't believe you!
我以为你不一样
I thought you were different...
我的花儿
my flower.
我曾努力帮你生长
I tried to help you grow.
但现在我明白了 你是野草 和她一样
But now I see you are a weed, just as she was.
嘿 有人来了
Hey! Someone's comin'!
你该离开了
You better get going.
汉普顿
Hampton.
回头见
I'll see you around.
来驯服这些脾气吧 混蛋们
Come and tame these tempers, assholes.
(德文斯科特来电)
塞尔维格太太 终于啊 我一直在找你
Mrs. Selvig? Thank fuck, I've been trying to reach you.
是 我知道
Yes, I'm aware.
听我说 马克在恢复记忆
So, listen, Mark has been reintegrating.
瑞伽比
Reghabi?
是的
Yeah.
她还没害死他
And she hasn't killed him yet?
没有 我觉得他似乎没事
No. I mean, I think he's okay?
但是 听着 我们想尝试另一个方法
But listen, we wanna try something else.
马克在你身边吗
Is Mark with you?
- 嗯哼 在 - 让他听电话
- Uh-huh. Yes. - Put him on.
是 喂
Yeah. Hello?
把一切都告诉我
Tell me everything.